[MUSIC]
(音乐)
Stanford University,
斯坦福大学,
>> Welcome to Standford CS 193P,
> >欢迎来到斯坦福CS 193便士,
Developing Applications for iOS, Winter of 2017,
iOS应用程序开发,2017年冬天,
This is lecture number 12, and
这是12号的讲座,
today our topic is going to be Autolayout,
今天我们的主题是自动布局,
I'm going to review a little bit of what we already know
我将回顾一些我们已经知道的东西
about Autolayout and
关于自动布局和
then move onto a very important part of auto layout
然后移动到一个非常重要的部分自动布局
called size classes then we'll demo everything as usual,
称为大小类然后我们将演示一切像往常一样,
What have you seen in Autolayout already?
在自动布局已经你看过什么?
Well, you know about the dash blue lines,
嗯,你知道dash蓝线,
When you drag things out and move them around and
当你拖动和移动它们
you make those dash blue lines appear you know that it helps
你让那些冲蓝线出现你知道它帮助
Xcode when you wanna do Reset to Suggested Constraints,
Xcode重置为建议限制,当你想做的
And you know that sometimes Reset to
你知道有时重置
Suggested Constraints doesn't really do what you want,
建议限制并没有真正做你想做的事情,
It really only works if those blue lines just unambiguously
真的只能如果这些蓝线明确
obviously,
很明显,
That's what you wanted,
这就是你想要的,
But you also know that after you do something,
但是你也知道,在你做一些事情,
especially after you do reset to suggest the constraints,
特别是在你重置为建议的约束,
you can go over to the Size Inspector and
你可以去督察和大小
click on any of the views in your UI and you
点击任何UI和你的意见
can look at the constraints and it shows you them,
可以看看约束和它向您展示了他们,
You can even kind of hover over them with the mouse and
你甚至可以用鼠标和上空盘旋
they will show them on the screen,
他们将显示在屏幕上,
Highlight them, etc,
强调他们,等,
So that's a good tool to know what's going on,
所以这是一个很好的工具,知道发生了什么,
You also know that you can click on the constraint
你也知道,你可以点击约束
itself,
本身,
The little I beams or whatever,
小我梁之类的,
you can click on them and bring up inspector on them and
你可以点击,弹出检查员和
you can see a lot of detail: what the constants are,
你可以看到很多细节:什么是常数,
what's on either end of them, in other words what
在两端,换句话说什么
the constraints, the two things being involved and
参与和约束,两件事
constrained are, so you already know that as well,
限制,所以你已经知道,
You also know about control dragging
你也知道控制拖
to edges, we did a lot of control dragging to the edge
边,我们做了很多控制拖到边缘
to make our UI kinda use up all the space but
使我们的UI但有点用完所有的空间
you also saw a little bit of a hint in the smashtag demo
你也看到一点点的提示smashtag演示
that you can actually control drag between any two views,
你可以控制阻力之间的任何两个观点,
This is the key thing about Autolayout,
自动布局,这是关键的事情
It sets constraints really between any two views,
真的集约束之间的任何两个观点,
There's really almost no restriction
其实几乎没有限制
between the things you can set constraints,
你可以设置约束之间的事情,
Again so we'll see that in the demo a little bit today,
所以我们会看到,在今天的演示一下,
Now in addition to control dragging to set up these
现在除了控制拖动设置
constraints between things, you can also select them,
约束之间的事情,你也可以选择它们,
I select one view or select a couple of views,
我选择一个视图或选择一些观点,
And there's a couple little menus in the corner down
角落里,有几个小菜单
there the pin menu or the align menu and
销菜单或菜单和对齐
then this other kinda generic menu that has a lot of random
然后这其他通用的菜单,有很多随机的
things you can set constraints for,
你可以设置约束,
And we'll use that today as well, so
今天,我们将使用,所以
you can see that different way of doing it,
你可以看到,不同的方法,
Pretty much everything in there you can do with
几乎有你能做的一切
Ctrl+drag, but sometimes it's hard to do Ctrl+drag,
Ctrl +拖,但有时很难做Ctrl +拖,
Maybe the views are very close together, or
也许视图非常接近,或
they're really near the edge,
他们真的在边缘附近,
or they're overlapping some other view,
或者他们重叠的其他视图,
And so when that starts to be a problem, you can
所以当开始成为一个问题,你可以
click on them to select, either using the control shift
点击选择,要么使用控制转变
click to drill down if things are overlapping, or
点击下钻如果重叠,或
maybe use the document outline to select it, and then go to
也许使用文档大纲以选择它,然后去
these menus to apply whatever constraints that you want,
这些菜单应用任何你想要的约束,
Now the document outline, we've showed briefly and
现在文档大纲,我们显示简要和
I'll show it again today, is really the go to place to
今天我将展示一遍,真的是去的地方
resolve problems with constraints,
解决问题与约束,
Both constraints that are insufficient, in other words
这两个约束不足,换句话说
you, you haven't put enough constraints on a view for
你,你还没有把足够的限制一个视图
the Xcode to or the IOS to know where the thing goes,
Xcode或IOS知道的事,
Or constraints that conflict,
或约束冲突,
Maybe you put two constraints on a views
也许你把两个限制的观点
that is like they're pulling against each other and
就像他们对彼此和
IOS doesn't know what to do,
IOS不知道要做什么,
So the document outline is the place to go to resolve
所以文档大纲是去解决的地方
all that stuff and we'll see that in the demo today,
所有这些,我们会看到,在今天的演示,
Now one thing to understand about autolayout is it takes
现在有一件事要理解自动布局是需要的
experience to master it,
经验来掌握它,
There's a lot of degrees of freedom there with those
有很多与这些自由度
constraints in terms of how you can
约束条件如何
constrain views relative to each other and
相对于彼此,限制的观点
there's just no substitute for experience,
只是不可替代的经验,
You just have to do it,
你只需要这样做,
So don't expect that after you see the demo today,
所以不要认为你今天看到的演示后,
And after what you've seen earlier in the course,
之后,你见过的,
Like, "now I am an auto layout master",
说,“现在我是一个自动布局大师”,
You will have to be designing a lot of user interfaces,
你必须设计一个用户界面,
Lining up a lot of edges,
排队的边缘,
Making things the same widths, those kinds of things,
做相同的宽度,这样的事情,
Until you learn kind of the tools enough to be a good
直到你学会一种足以是一个很好的工具
auto layout master,
自动布局的主人,
But once you master it,
但是一旦你掌握它,
it can be really really super powerful as you can see,
它可以真的超级强大的正如你所看到的,
Autolayout is also doable from code,
从代码自动布局也是可行的,
In other words, there is a class and
换句话说,有一个类和
it's layout constraint and
这是约束和布局
it has all the functionality is in the story board,
它的所有功能在故事板,
We rarely use it because we can do
我们很少使用它,因为我们可以做
pretty much anything from a story board,
几乎任何一个故事板,
But I'm not gonna have time to teach it,
但是我不会有时间教,
Obviously I have to be selective about what
显然,我必须选择什么
I can show you in this limited time available,
我可以带你在这有限的时间,
But you can do some pretty tricky things in code that
但是你可以在代码做一些很棘手的事情
you can't do in storyboard, but they're pretty, I don't
你不能在故事板,但是他们漂亮,我不喜欢
want to say advanced, but they are, let's say fairly obscure,
想说先进,但是他们是,假设相当模糊,
And so, if you're interested in pursuing that, maybe for
所以,如果你感兴趣,也许
your final project, or
你最后的项目,或
something, you can just start with NSLayout constraint in
一些东西,你可以从NSLayout约束
the documentation, and kind of go from there,
文档,从那里开始,
Let's talk a little about rotation, auto rotation,
让我们谈一下旋转,自动旋转,
We know that when we rotate, that's one of the biggest
我们知道,当我们旋转,这是最大的一个
times that autolayout has to kick in and figure out where
次自动布局和找出踢
things go because things have dramatically changed,
去,因为事情已经发生了巨大的变化,
They're much wider than they are tall now or vice versa,
他们是更广泛的比现在高,反之亦然,
And sometimes unfortunately,
有时很不幸,
that rotation causes such a dramatic change in your UI
旋转导致这样一个戏剧性的变化在你的UI
that you want to actually move views around in a way that you
其实你想移动视图的方式
just can't say by align these edges, make these the same
只是不能说通过对齐这些边缘,使这些相同的
width, keep this separation, those kinds of things,
宽度,保持这种分离,这样的事情,
You actually want to pick them up and move them,
你真的想拾起并移动它们,
And actually, a great example of that is our calculator,
实际上,一个很好的例子,这是我们的计算器,
Our calculator, at least, not your calculator but
我们的计算器,至少不是你的计算器
the calculator we last saw in demo had 20 buttons, and
我们上次见到的计算器演示有20按钮、和
we had it as four across and five down,
我们把它当作四,五,
And that made a lot of sense because
做了很多有意义的,因为
in portrait mode we had a lot of vertical space and
在竖屏模式,我们有很多的垂直空间
not a lot of horizontal space, so we kinda went for the,
没有太多的水平空间,所以我们有点的,
The five high, four wide,
五个高,宽四,
But when we switch to landscape, now it's not so
但当我们切换到景观,现在不是这样的
good, cuz all of the buttons are squished down,
好,因为所有的按钮都是扁平的,
They're really wide and thin,
他们真的又宽又薄,
It would be much better if when we get to landscape,
这将是更好的,如果当我们到达风景,
we could go to five across and
5,我们可以去
four down because we have a lot less space,
4因为我们有很多更少的空间,
Now, can you imagine trying to do a control drag to
现在,你能想象试图控制阻力
make that happen is basically impossible,
实现这个目标基本上是不可能的,
It can't be done,
不能完成,
But it's possible to do with a very important
但也有可能与一个非常重要的
feature which I'm gonna talk about in a moment here,
功能,一会儿我要讲,
Now, this kind of rotation stuff is,
现在,这种旋转的东西,
the problem where your view changes from landscape
视图从景观变化的问题
to portrait and you wanna move all the views around
肖像,你想移动的所有视图
can happen in other situations too,
也可以发生在其他情况下,
Imagine that you have an MVC that wants to look good in
假设您有一个MVC,想看起来不错
Landscape, but also wants to look good when it's the master
景观,还想看起来不错的主
of a Split View Controller,
分屏视图控制器,
The master of a Split View Controller kind of looks likes
的主人看起来喜欢拆分视图控制器
it's in portrait, so even though you're on an iPad,
肖像,所以即使你在iPad上,
let's say, sometimes you have tall and
比方说,有时你高大
skinny, just like what you have on an iPhone,
瘦,就像你在iPhone上,
So it's not just iPhone issue only or rotation issue only,
所以这不仅仅是iPhone只或旋转问题问题,
So, the solution to all this is called size classes,
因此,所有这叫做大小类的解决方案,
Now, Apple has chosen to take an approach to dealing with
现在,苹果公司选择一个方法来处理
this which is fairly simple,
这是相当简单的,
Which is a pretty good idea because you could imagine
这是一个不错的主意,因为你可以想象吗
a very complicated solution that tries to, basically, take
一个非常复杂的解决方案,试图,基本上,
into effect every possible geometry and every size,
每一个可能的几何和每一个尺寸,
You could end up writing a lot of code or a massive number
你可能会写很多代码或者一个巨大的数字
of auto layout constraints to make it work,
自动布局的限制使它工作,
So they've boiled it down to this very simple system
所以他们煮这个非常简单的系统
where they talk about size classes and a view or
他们讨论类和视图或大小
a view controller at any given time exists with
一个视图控制器存在在任何给定的时间
a certain size class,
一定规模类,
Both in the horizontal direction and
在水平方向上和
the vertical direction,
垂直方向,
And the only two values that the size class can have is
唯一的类可以有两个值的大小
compact or regular,
或普通紧凑,
So regular is regular sized, and
所以常规是常规尺寸,
compact means that you're constrained in that direction,
简洁意味着你在这个方向约束,
Let's look at all our devices and
让我们看看我们所有的设备和
see when they're constrained in either compact
看到当他们限制在紧凑
in either height or width, and when they're just regular,
在高度或宽度,当他们只是普通的,
Let's talk about the iPhone first the iPhone in portraits
首先让我们来谈谈iPhone肖像的iPhone
is regular in height, plenty of height, but
身高一般、足够的高度,但
it's compact in width,
紧凑的宽度,
It's kinda constrained in width in that circumstance,
在这种情况下,有点宽限制
When you switch to landscape, maybe surprisingly,
当你切换到景观,也许令人惊讶的是,
iPhones are compact in both directions because even though
iphone在两个方向,因为即使紧凑
when you go to landscape, it gets quite a bit wider,
当你去风景,它变得相当宽,
it's still not that wide,
它还不宽,
Okay, it's not wide like an iPad,
好吧,这不是宽像iPad一样,
It's still somewhat constrained, so
还是有些限制,所以
they've decided to make landscape
他们已经决定格局
iPhone be compact in both directions,
iPhone是在两个方向上紧凑,
So in portrait it's regular in height and compact in width,
所以在肖像定期在宽度、高度和紧凑
But in Landscape, it's compacted both directions,
但在景观,压实两个方向,
We will encounter into it but
我们会遇到,但是
just see it works out quite nicely,
看看它的工作原理很好地,
Now, the iPhone +s, the 6+ and
现在,iPhone +年代,6 +和
the 7+, those are a little different,
这是有点不同的,7 +
They're still compact in width,
他们仍然紧凑的宽度,
And regular in height in portrait but
和定期在肖像但高度
when you go to landscape,
当你去风景,
since those iPhone pluses are so
因为这些iPhone有利
big, that they can actually start showing that kind of
大,他们可以开始出现的
horizontal UI just like it was an iPad or something,
水平的UI就像iPad之类的,
So they are regular in width in landscape mode,
所以他们定期在横向模式宽度,
iPhone is compact in both,
iPhone是在紧凑,
The iPhone Plus, still compact in height, in landscape, but
iPhone +,仍然高度紧凑,在景观,但
it's regular in width,
常规的宽度,
Then the iPad,
然后iPad,
Since it's huge, is always regular in both dimensions,
因为它是巨大的,总是经常在这两个维度,
Both width and height is always irregular, but
宽度和高度都是不规则的,但是
that's only for
这只是对
new controllers that are taking over the whole screen,
新控制器接管整个屏幕,
If your view controller,
如果你的视图控制器,
like I said in the master of a split view,
就像我说的在拆分视图的主人,
you're compact width, regular height,
你习惯紧凑的宽度,高度,
Or if your multi-tasking MVC that comes out from the right,
或者如果你多任务MVC从右边出来,
you all know about multi-tasking
大家都知道多任务
in the iPad hopefully,
iPad的希望
You can drag anything out from the right and
你可以拖动任何权利和
pick another app, and have two apps running side by side,
选择另一个应用程序,有两个并排运行的应用程序,
Well, when you pull that thing out,
好吧,当你把那件事,
that's also gonna be a compact width, regular height,
这也将是一个紧凑的宽度,常规的高度,
Now this whole mechanism of Compact and Regular in
现在这整个机制的紧凑和常规
size classes, of course, it's built-in for devices as I've
大小类,当然,正如我是内置的设备
described above here, but it's also extensible,
上面描述的,但也是可扩展的,
So if you were to write your own thing where an MVC was
所以如果你要写自己的事MVC在哪里
embedded inside another MVC,
嵌入另一个MVC,
You could set or
你可以设置或
communicate whether that MVC is compact or regular,
MVC紧凑或是否定期交流,
In each of width and
在每一个宽度和
height and kind of send a message to the MVC,
高度和发送消息的MVC,
Hey I've constrained your height so
嘿我约束你的身高
make sure you deal with that,
确保你处理,
Or I've constrained your width,
或者我约束你的宽度,
And so, it can react to it,
因此,它可以反应,
Now, again, I'm not gonna have time to talk about that
现在,再一次,我不会有时间去讨论
in detail, but there is this bar called trait collection
详细,但这条叫做特征集合
which you can look at in a view controller,
在一个视图控制器,你可以看看
And it will tell you what your current size class is,
它会告诉你什么是你当前的大小类,
both horizontally and vertically,
从水平和垂直方向上,
And there's a mechanism for
的机制
passing that along down to sub MVCs and views and things,
传递到子mvc和观点和事情,
We have the size classes, compact width and
我们有大小类、宽度和紧凑
regular width, compact height and regular height,
常规的宽度、高度和定期高度紧凑,
which makes for four different combinations right here and
这使得这里的四种不同的组合和
again, compact width and
再次,紧凑的宽度和
height is iPhones in landscape but not plus ones,
高度是iphone在景观而不是加的,
Compact height and
紧凑的高度和
regular width is the iPhone plus only in landscape,
常规的宽度是iPhone加上只在景观,
Regular height and compact width is iPhones in portrait,
常规的高度和宽度是iphone在肖像紧凑,
both plusses and regular and also like a split view master,
分和定期和也喜欢拆分视图的主人,
And then regular regular is an iPad in portrait or
然后定期定期在肖像或iPad
landscape, the whole thing,
风景,整件事情,
So if we had this normal grid and we wanted our calculator
如果我们有这个正常的网格和我们想要我们的计算器
to look good in all of them conceivably we'd have to
看起来很好,他们可以想象我们必须
write, do four different UIs for our calculator like this,
写,四个不同的ui为我们这样的计算器,
When I Have some more vertical height,
当我有一些更多的垂直高度,
I go five high but
我去五高但
when I'm kind of compacted I'll go to only four high,
当我压实的我要去只有四个高,
So this would be a bit of a pain in the neck to have to do
这是有点讨厌,必须要做的事情
To make it a little easier, when we are designing,
使它更容易,当我们正在设计,
this,
这一点,
we also have the concept of any height or any width,
我们也有任何高度或宽度的概念,
Now if we do that, now we're down to only having to do two
如果我们这样做,我们现在只需要做两个
things with our calculator,
我们的计算器,
So anytime we have compact height and we don't care
所以只要我们有紧凑的高度和我们不关心
what the width is, we're going to go four high,
宽度是什么,我们要四高,
Anytime we have regular height and
只要我们有规律的高度和
we don't care what the width is, we'll go five high,
我们不关心宽度是什么,我们就去五高,
So that's reduced the amount of work we have to do by half,
这就是我们要做的工作量减少了一半,
And actually we can reduce it even more because we can also
实际上我们可以减少它更多,因为我们也可以
design any any,
设计任何任何,
This any by the way doesn't mean any like the Swift
这一切并不意味着任何迅速
type "any", it just means any width, any height,
输入“任何”,它只是意味着任何宽度,高度,
the English word any,
英文单词,
And so we can do our designing and in fact our default design
所以我们可以做设计和事实上默认设计
in storyboards is to be designing any width,
在故事板设计任何宽度,
any height,
任何高度,
that are the same for the five wide case or the four wide
相同的五宽情况下或四宽
case, we can build all that in the any any mode,
情况下,我们可以构建所有,在任何模式下,
And then only have to do the stuff that's specific to
然后只需要做具体的东西
the size class being different in that case,
在这种情况下,类大小不同
So, that reduces even more the design we have to do,
这减少了更多的设计我们要做的,
Cuz we're doing most of our design any any,
因为我们正在做我们的大部分设计任何任何,
and then a little bit to make the other two work,
然后一点点让另外两个工作,
So, you can see it in the calculator here, the only
所以,你可以看到它在这里的计算器,唯一
things I can do in any/any is the base keyboard there, not
我可以做的事情在任何/键盘底部,没有
including the buttons that are either gonna be on the top or
包括按钮,会在顶部或
because those depending on the vertical size class there,
因为这些大小取决于垂直类,
on the side,
在方面,
And also I can do my display at the top,
我还可以做我的显示在顶部,
If that's all I can do,
如果这是我所能做的,
But most of my UI we'll see in the demo I'll do exactly this,
但是我的大多数UI在演示中我们会看到我做的正是这一点,
That's a lot,
这是很多,
Let's jump into that,
让我们进入,
To make the demo a little easier to understand what's
使演示更容易理解
going on here the developer, here's our calculator,
这里的开发人员,这是我们的计算器,
I actually added a little
我添加了一个小
bit of code to my calculator and
我的计算器和一些代码
I'll show it to you,
我会告诉你,
This is the calculator that we've left off,
这是我们离开,计算器
The last thing we did in this calculator was
计算器是我们做的最后一件事
the green square root,
绿色的平方根,
Remember so it was not changed since then except for this,
记住这并不改变之后,除了这,
In the view controller for this guy,
视图控制器的这个家伙,
I added this blue code right here,
我添加了这个蓝色的代码,
I added this function showSizeClasses
我添加了这个函数showSizeClasses
which hijacks the display,
劫持的显示,
You know our blue display on the top, it hijacks it and
你知道我们的蓝色显示在顶部,它和劫持
writes in there what the width and
在宽度和写道
height size classes are of the calculator in the moment okay,
高度尺寸类是计算器的时刻,
And then I just Implemented a couple of ViewController
然后我就实现几个ViewController
life-cycle methods here, viewDidAppear calls it,
生命周期方法,viewDidAppear调用它,
And then, view will transition to size,
然后,视图将过渡到大小,
which is what happens when you rotate,
当你旋转时,就会发生这样的事
And I just call this showSizeClasses there,
我就叫这个showSizeClasses那里,
I also added a little extension to
我还添加了一个小扩展
UI user interface size class to just have it
用户界面UI类就有大小
implement custom string convertible,
实现自定义字符串转换,
So it implements that method description,
它实现了这一方法的描述,
And just returns compact and regular,
就返回紧凑和常规,
That's so that I can do this line of code right here,
这样我可以做这行代码,
where I'm printing out the size classes,
我打印大小类,
So, it's not really important that you understand this,
所以,这不是很重要,你明白这一点,
You'll just notice that when we run it,
您会注意到,当我们运行它,
So I'll go ahead and run here,
所以我要继续运行,
You're gonna see that that blue thing is gonna get
你会看到那个蓝色的东西
taken over to show you the size class,
接管给你大小类,
It's just cuz when you're running I want you to be clear
只是因为当你跑步我要你清楚
on what size classes we're doing both horizontally and
在我们做的水平和规模类
vertically,
垂直,
When we are in, and this is iPhone 7, So we are in
当我们在,这是iPhone 7,所以我们都在
portrait mode, so you can see that our width is compact and
竖屏模式,所以你可以看到,我们的宽度是紧凑,
our height is regular,
我们的高度是常规,
If I rotate, so I'm just gonna hit the Cmd key here,
如果我旋转,所以这里我要按Cmd键,
rotate, you can see that now we are width compact and
旋转,你可以看到,现在我们宽度和紧凑
height compact cuz we're on the iPhone 7,
高度紧凑的因为我们在iPhone上7,
If we were on iPhone 7 Plus,
如果我们在iPhone上7 +,
right now it would be width regular height compact,
现在它将宽度固定高度紧凑,
So, in the interest of time I won't run there,
因此,由于时间关系我就不跑,
but when we do come to running it we'll be able to always see
但当我们做来运行它,我们总能看到
what size class we're in,
什么大小,我们班
So, here is our UI right here,
所以,这是我们的UI,
And there's a couple of things we can do with size classes
有几件事情我们可以做的尺寸类
that are actually really, really simple,
真的,真的很简单,
For example, you can click on certain UI elements,
例如,您可以点击特定的UI元素,
like a label, and when you go to the attribute inspector
像一个标签,当你去属性检查器
over here you'll notice that some of the attributes have
在这里你会注意到的一些属性
these little pluses,
这些小的优点,
See that? Plus, plus?
看到了吗?
And down here, plus and plus?
在这里,+和+ ?
And what these pluses let you do,
这些优点让你做什么,
is change these fields in that size clause,
改变这些字段大小条款,
We can do the any/any,
我们可以做任何/,
We can do compact with compact height any,
我们能做的紧凑与紧凑的高度,
any combination we want,
我们想要的,任意组合
So for example here, let's go ahead and
举个例子,让我们继续
have our background color of our display up here
我们显示的背景颜色了吗
vary depending on our height size class,
取决于我们的高度尺寸类,
If we're height compact, we'll do one thing,
如果我们高度紧凑,我们会做一件事,
If we're height regular we'll do another,
如果我们高度定期做另一个,
So, we do that by pressing this little plus,
所以,我们按这个小加,
You see when you do that,
你看,当你这样做,
And here we can pick the width that we want,
在这里,我们可以选择我们想要的宽度,
And since we're varying on the height I'm just gonna say
因为我们在不同的高度我只是想说
any width,
任何宽度,
And I'm gonna say height compact, so this will,
我会说高度紧凑,这将
means that this background that it's gonna,
意味着这样的背景之下,它会,
this variation it's gonna create,
这种变化将创建,
will only take effect when the height is compact,
只会生效时高度紧凑,
if the height is regular, this is not going to take effect,
如果高度是常规,这是不会生效,
So, I'm gonna add a variation, you see it added it here,
所以,我会添加一个变异,你看到它补充说,
you see the little hC,
你看到小hC,
that means height compact all right, the width is any, so
这意味着高度紧凑,宽度是任何,所以
it doesn't say anything about width,
它没有说任何关于宽度,
And now we can change it,
现在我们可以改变它,
Let's pick, this is for high compact, so
让我们挑选,这是高紧凑,所以
I'm going to pick cyan,
我要选择青色,
C for cyan, C for compact,
青色C,C紧凑,
hopefully you can remember that,
希望你能记住,
So, I've changed that,
所以,我改变了这一切,
Now, when I changed this, notice nothing changed here,
现在,当我改变了这个数字,注意这里并没有什么改变,
Why did nothing change there?
为什么没有改变?
Anyone know?
有人知道吗?
It's because we are in portrait on an iPhone here,
这是因为我们在肖像在iPhone上,
iPhone portrait, that is size class height regular, see,
iPhone的肖像,这是大小类高度固定,看,
down here it will always tell you what your size class is or
这里它总是告诉你你的类或大小
what you are looking at this is height regular,
你看这是高度常规,
So, since height regular is not height compact,
所以,既然高度常规不是高度紧凑,
we get the default,
默认的,
But if I switch over to here, landscape, it turned cyan,
但是如果我切换到这里,风景,它变成了青色,
Because now, I'm in landscape mode of an iPhone,
因为现在,我在iPhone的景观模式,
which is height compact, width compact, as well,
这是高度紧凑,宽度紧凑,,
And if I go to iPhone 7, is it gonna be cyan here?
如果我去iPhone 7,将青色吗?
Yes, it is, because in iPhone 7 Plus, we're regular width,
是的,它是,因为在iPhone 7 +,我们常规的宽度,
but we're still compact height,
但我们仍然高度紧凑,
so we're still getting that cyan there,
所以我们还在那青色,
Now, we could add another one, for example, right here,
现在,我们可以添加另一个,例如,在这里,
we could go add this one and say, what about any width and
我们可以添加这个,说什么任何宽度和
height is regular add a variation for that and
高度是定期添加一个变异和
go up here maybe we'll pick red for regular, and so
走在这里也许我们会选择红色的定期,所以
now any time the height is regular we're gonna see red,
现在任何时候高是正常我们会看到红色,
So let's go look at potrait>iPhone 7 Plus
所以我们去看写作者> iPhone 7 +
that's clearly regular,
这是明显规律,
How about iPad?
iPad呢?
Red, It's regular,
红色,它的常规,
Let's go iPhone,
让我们去iPhone,
Red, Regular height,
红色,常规的高度,
Let's go landscape,
让我们去风景,
Back to compact, so we get cyan,
回到紧凑,所以我们得到青色,
So you see how I'm just adding these variations,
所以你看到我只是增加了这些变化,
And you can do that for lots of different things,
你可以做很多不同的东西,
For example, when we look at this UI on an iPad,
例如,当我们看这个UI在iPad上,
it doesn't look that good,
它看起来不那么好,
Because, look how tiny all the fonts are here,
因为,看小字体都在这里,
Maybe we would want to go up here and add a variation when
也许我们会想去这里,当添加一个变化
it's regular, regular, okay, iPad only,
定期,定期,iPad,
where we increase the font on the buttons up to 80 or 90,
我们增加按钮上的字体到80年或90年,
We could do that,
我们可以这样做,
That's not always gonna be the best way to do things like
这并不是总是会做事情的最佳方式
vary your font, but it's certainly possible to do that,
改变你的字体,但当然可以这样做,
Understand all that business?
理解所有的业务吗?
So, let's talk a little bit of how we are going to make this
让我们谈谈我们是如何让这个
UI do the five by four or the four by five thing here,
UI做五个由四个或者四个五个的事情,
And we know that we want to have as much
我们知道我们想要
of the UI as we can that's common to both be shared,
常见的UI我们可以共享,
So, what I'm gonna do is try to
所以,我要做的是试着什么
work on that shared part of the UI here,
在这里共享UI的一部分工作,
And it doesn't really matter what device I'm looking at
它并不重要设备我看什么
while I'm doing this,
当我这样做,
Could be a iPhone Plus,
可能是一个iPhone +,
could be a regular iPhone, doesn't matter,
可能是一个常规的iPhone,无所谓,
because I'm editing stuff that applies to all size classes,
因为我编辑尺寸适用于所有类的东西,
And I'll show you in a moment how we're gonna edit stuff
一会儿,我将向您展示如何我们要编辑的东西
that applies to a specific size class,
适用于一个特定的大小类,
So how I'm gonna do this,
那么我要如何做到这一点,
you saw in the slides that really only this
你看到的真的只有这个幻灯片
part right here, these bottom 16 are common to all,
部分,这些底16是常见的,
These four across the top are either across the top or
这四个在顶部或顶部
they're off, off to the left in a horizontally compact
他们,在水平向左紧凑
situation,
情况,
I'm gonna kind of have to unbundle all these things, so
我将不得不将所有这些东西,所以
let's start by just selecting this top level StackView and
让我们首先选择这个顶级StackView和
unstackviewifying it,
unstackviewifying它,
Take everything out of the StackView because clearly
把一切都StackView因为很明显
these things can't be inside that StackView,
这些东西不能StackView里面,
And one thing to understand when you're doing these
一件事理解当你在做这些
size classes, you can have views come and
大小的类,你可以过来的看法
go based on size classes, but you can't have them come and
基于大小类,但你不能来
go inside StackViews,
进入StackViews,
It doesn't know how to put a view in inside another view,
它不知道如何将一个视图在在另一个视图中,
It has to be kind of a top level, coming and going, or
它必须是一种顶级,来来往往,或
inclusion or not inclusion,
包含或不包含,
So, how do we undo a stack view?
那么,我们如何撤销堆栈视图?
Actually you can just go to editor up here,
其实你可以去编辑,
the same place that we said embed in stack view,
相同的地方,我们说嵌入在堆栈视图中,
you can actually do unembed and that will take everything
你可以做unembed,将一切
out of stack view, back to where we were before,
堆栈视图,回到以前,
The other thing I'm gonna do is I'm gonna get rid of
另一件我要做的就是我要摆脱
all the constraints on here, cuz I had these constraints
这里所有的约束,因为我有这些约束
that were holding this to the edge, but they just don't
拿着这个边缘,但他们只是不
make any sense anymore cuz I've unbundled this,
任何意义了因为我分类定价,
So, how can I do that?
所以,我怎么能这样做呢?
Right down here in the lower corner where it says resolve
下在较低的角落它说的决心
auto layout issues,
自动布局问题,
You can go down here and
你可以在这里
for all views in the view controller,
所有视图的视图控制器,
you can say clear constraints,
你可以说明确的约束,
So that's what I'm gonna go and
这就是我要去
it's gonna wipe out all the constraints in this
它会消灭所有的约束
view controller,
视图控制器,
Clear them all out,
都清楚了,
So now that I don't have the constraints in here,
所以现在我在这里,没有约束
I can move this staff around and kind of put
我可以移动这个员工,把
new constraints that I want on here and we can see that our
新的约束,我希望在这里我们可以看到
constraints are cleared because if I select something
约束被清除,因为如果我选择的东西
like this top label and I go to size inspector over here,
像上面的标签和我去尺寸检查器,
there's no constraint at the bottom,
没有约束的底部,
So let's go ahead and move this out of the way,
所以让我们继续和移动的方式,
Let's put this back tied to the top and
我们把这个与顶部和回来
left and right in exactly the same way as we did before,
左翼和右翼在我们之前做的完全一样,
So to kind of review,
这样的评论,
I'm just gonna control drag to the top notch,
我要控制拖动到顶尖,
I'm gonna do something interesting,
我要做一些有趣的事情,
I'm gonna Ctrl+Drag kinda up to the corner up here,
我要按Ctrl +有点拖到角落里,
When I do that, I can actually do both leading and
当我这样做,我可以做领导和
vertical space,
垂直空间,
And what I'm doing here to make,
我在这里做的,
to pick more than one constraint, is Shift,
选择多个约束,转变,
So, if you do Shift, you can pick more than one thing,
所以,如果你做改变,你可以选择一个以上的东西,
So here, I want both the leading edge on the left
这里,我想要两个左边的前缘
there, and the top edge,
,顶部边缘,
the vertical space to be tied, to be constrained,
相关的垂直空间,约束,
So, I just pick all the ones I want and then I click
所以,我只选择我想要的,然后我点击
add constraints right here, and it adds those two,
添加约束,它增加了这两个,
And same thing, I can do this one over here then,
同样的事情,我可以做这个,
That's the trailing one,
拖着一个,
So now, when we look at our label up there,
现在,当我们看标签,
it's got these constraints,
它有这些限制,
That's good, that's what we want,
这很好,这就是我们想要的,
Now, what about this bottom constraint?
现在,这个底部约束呢?
Well, it use to be that the bottom of this was tied to
它使用,这是相关的底部
the top of this, and
的这个,
then the bottom of this was tied to the bottom of this,
然后与底部的底部,
But we can't do that anymore,
但是我们不能这样做了,
Because in five high by four wide, this is
因为在五高四宽,这是
gonna be on the top, but in four high and five wide,
会在上面,但在四个高,宽五,
these are gonna be over here and this is gonna be the top,
这些都是要在这里这是顶部,
So that's something we can't do in the any/any mode,
这是我们不能做的事在任何/模式,
We just can't do it,
我们不能这样做,
But we can take this stack down view and
但我们可以把这个堆栈视图和
put it down in this corner over here,
把它放在这里,这个角落
And use our same control drags
使用相同的控制拖
to do the trailing space there, and
那里的尾随空格,
the control drag to the bottom
控制拖到底部
to do the vertical space,
垂直空间,
So I've tied this thing to the bottom,
所以我把这个东西,
So this actually works, in quotes,
这确实有效,在报价,
it works in both modes,
它能在两种模式下运行,
Keeps them both on screen it's doing what I said keeping
让他们两个在屏幕上做我所说的保持
the display at the top and
顶部的显示
keeping this stuff in the lower right,
在右下角,
But it's clearly insufficient to do what we want in the two
但它显然不足以做我们想做的事
So, in the two cases, it's this stack view right here,
所以,在这两种情况下,这里的堆栈视图,
different cases,
不同的情况下,
let me zoom in a little,
让我放大一点,
This stack view right here is the one that's at issue,
这个堆栈视图是一个问题,
So I'm just gonna take this thing and
所以我要把这个东西
lift it up out of the stack view, which you can do,
把它从堆栈视图中,你可以做,
you can lift things up and out,
你能举起的东西,
So I lift it out and drop it, and it's sitting there,
所以我把它放,坐在那里,
Now it doesn't want to be in the any, any case at all,
现在不想要任何,任何情况下,
It wants to only be in certain size classes,
它希望只有在特定的大小类,
So, I'm going to take it and cut it, because I'm gonna
所以,我要把它切它,因为我要
paste it back in when we get to other size classes,
粘贴在其他大小类别时,
So this is our any/any right here,
这是我们这里的任何/,
This is the best we can do in terms of common UI to both
这是最好的我们可以做的两种常见的UI
the compact vertical case, and the regular vertical case,
紧凑的垂直情况下,常规的垂直情况下,
Now let's go on and do the compact case let's say,
现在让我们继续和紧凑的情况下假设,
Let's do the UI that's compact,
让我们做的UI紧凑,
Now since all the work that we're going to be doing right
既然所有的工作,我们要做的是正确的
now is only for the compact case we depress this super
现在是紧凑的情况下,我们只有这个超级压低
important button right here, vary for traits,
重要的按钮,不同的特征,
This, this is what it's all about when it comes to doing
这个,这是都是什么时候做的
the size class variations,
类大小变化,
So first you're gonna pick something that has the height
首先你要选择具有高度的东西
or width class or both that you want to vary,
或宽类或你想要改变,
So here I wanna do the horizontally or
这里我想做水平或
the height compact, see height compact, I wanna do that one,
高度紧凑,看到高度紧凑的,我想做这个,
So this is a pretty good one to work in, but
这是一个很好的工作,但是
I can pick any of the ones that are height compact,
我可以选择任何的高度紧凑,
And I'm gonna say vary for traits,
我会说不同的特征,
And I'm gonna vary in the height direction,
我要在高度方向上不同,
Notice that that bar at the bottom turned bright blue,
请注意,底部栏变成明亮的蓝色,
That's to warn you, " watch out here
这是警告你,”看
now because you are editing UI only for height compact",
现在只因为你正在编辑界面高度紧凑的”,
And it's even showing you all devices that
甚至还显示你所有设备
are height compact,
是高度紧凑,
Which is all the iPhones, including the pluses,
这是所有的iphone,包括优点,
They're all in landscape, they're all height compact,
他们都在景观,它们都是高度紧凑,
and those are the only ones,
这些是唯一,
So all the editing we're doing now is only going to have
所以我们现在正在做的所有编辑只会
effect on these devices until we stop making this thing blue
影响这些设备,直到我们停止生产这个蓝色的
by pressing done varying,
按不同,
So, building this UI now we can, here's the two
这个UI现在我们可以建设,这是两个
big things you can do when in the blue mode here,
大事情你可以在蓝色的模式,
One is you can add views or remove views actually, and
一个是您可以添加视图或删除视图实际上,和
the other you can add constraints,
您可以添加约束,
So, that's exactly what I wanna do here,
所以,这就是我想做的,
I wanna put those four buttons over here,
我想把这四个按钮,
And then we wanna do some constraints to make those
然后我们要做一些让这些约束
buttons be in the right place,
按钮是在正确的地方,
So let's start by adding these back, remember I cut them so
让我们开始通过添加这些回来,记得我把它们
I'm just gonna paste,
我要粘贴,
Here it is, here's that stack view that had them,
这是,这是堆栈视图,让他们
It used to be inside this stack view at the top,
以前在这个堆栈视图在顶部,
Now we wanna kinda put it on this side,
现在我们想把它放在这方面,
And when I put it on this side I want it to like
当我把它放在这方面我希望它喜欢
seem like it's inside the stack view,
似乎是在堆栈视图,
but I can't actually put it inside the stack view,
但是我不能把它内部堆栈视图,
Cuz like I said, this variation for
因为就像我说的,这种变化
traits cannot put things inside stock views,
不能把事情在股票的言论,
But it's a great opportunity for
但这是一个伟大的机会
me to show you other auto layout constraints that can
我告诉你其他自动布局约束
make it seem like it's in that stack view,
使它看起来像在堆栈视图,
And basically do the same thing that the stock view is
基本上股票的观点是做同样的事情
doing internally which is just adding auto layout constraints
做内部就是添加自动布局约束
to make things work,
使事情工作,
Now the first thing we want is we want these buttons to be
现在我们想的第一件事是我们想要这些按钮
vertical,
纵向
We want them up and down and that's simple to do,
我们希望他们简单,上下
We have this selected,
我们有一个选择,
I'm just gonna go to the attributes inspector and
我要去属性检查器
change the stack view to be vertical,
改变垂直堆栈视图,
So it's switching over to vertical,
切换到垂直,
that's a really good start,
这是一个很好的开始,
I could drag this up next to it and use the blue lines,
我可以拖这旁边,用蓝线,
That's nice, although the blue lines are probably not gonna
这很好,虽然蓝线可能不会
get it right here,
在这里,
If you notice when I drop that blue line down, look,
如果你注意到当我把蓝线,看,
it's trying to do all kinds of things,
尝试各种各样的东西,
Centering here, stuff like that along the bottom,
定心,诸如此类的底部,
No, so I'm gonna do all my constraints here to make
没有,所以我要做我所有的约束条件
this hook up, I'm gonna do them all manually,
这个钩子,我要做手工,
Also it's a good chance to show you how to do them all,
也这是一个很好的机会向您展示如何做,
So what, how are we gonna make this vertical piece right
那么,我们要如何使垂直这一块
here, this vertical stack view,
在这里,这个垂直堆栈视图,
look like it's a part of this other stack view?
看起来这是一个其他堆栈视图的一部分吗?
One thing we want to do is we clearly want the height of
我们想要做的一件事就是我们显然想要的高度
this stack view to always be tracking the height of
这个堆栈视图总是跟踪的高度
the other one,
另一个,
We want the top and bottom edges, basically, of this
我们想要的顶部和底部边缘,基本上,这一点
stack view and of this stack view to always be pinned,
堆栈视图和堆栈视图总是固定的,
Well that sounds, pinning, sounds like a constraint,
那声音,锁住,听起来像一个约束,
We wanna constrain them, so, how can we do that?
我们想要约束他们,所以,我们该怎么做?
Here's how we do it, we're gonna select them both,
这是我们如何做,我们会选择它们,
A good way to select things, by the way, is dragging,
的一个好方法选择的事情,顺便说一下,拖着,
Dragging is a great way to select things,
拖是一个伟大的选择方式,
So I'm gonna select both of them right here,
所以我要选择他们两人在这里,
And then I'm gonna use this menu down here,
然后我要用下面这个菜单,
Which is called the align menu, and that's exactly what
叫做调整菜单,这是什么
I wanna do, I wanna align these things,
我想做,我想使这些事情,
I click on it, and you can see that I can align things like
我点击它,你可以看到,我可以对齐之类的东西
the centers or even the text base lines,
甚至文本中心基地,
But what I want here is that I wanna align the top
但是我想要的是我想让最高
and bottom,
和底部,
So I'm gonna click top and bottom,
所以我要点击顶部和底部,
These numbers over here by the way are an offset,
这些数字在这里顺便提一下一个偏移量,
So if you wanted it to align the tops but
如果你想要它顶部对齐
you want one to be ten higher, you can put a ten in here,
十高,你想要一个你可以把一百一十年在这里,
But I want them be right along the top,
但我希望他们是对的在顶部,
I wanna have the constraint where this is
我想这是有约束
exactly the same, this is exactly the same at all times,
完全相同的,这是完全相同的,
So I pick whichevers I want and
所以我选择哪个我要和
just say, add constraints and I added them,
只是说,添加约束和我说他们,
Now, woah,
现在,哇,
it turn red, why am I getting those red lines right there?
它变红了,为什么我得到那些红线?
Now, you can always find out about your
现在,你总是可以找到你
problems that you have with constraints by clicking on
通过点击问题与约束
this little thing right up here,
这个小东西,
You see this yellow guy, click on him and it says,
你看到这个黄色的家伙,点击他,它说,
the horizontal position is ambiguous for stack view,
堆栈视图的水平位置不明确,
Well, I've got multiple stack views, so
我有多个堆栈视图,所以
which one's it talking about,
哪一个的谈论,
This is kind of a bummer,
这是一种劣势,
This is really just an overview of the errors,
这只是一个概述的错误,
Usually we don't look here,
通常我们不看这里,
The place we look is in the document outline okay,
文档大纲的地方我们是好的,
The document outline here which I have shown,
这里的文档大纲我已经表明,
I can hide it and show it,
我可以隐藏和显示它,
This is the place where for
这是对的地方
example we had to wire up to the refresh control,
例子我们必须刷新控制连接,
This is the place we go when it's hard to click on
这是我们去的地方当很难点击
something, cuz we can just click on a view here,
什么,因为我们可以在这里点击视图,
This is also the place we go to deal with all auto
这也是我们去处理所有的汽车的地方
layout problems,
布局问题,
And the magic place to look is this upper corner right here,
神奇的地方是这里的上角,
You see that red right there?
你看到那个红色的?
This red is saying that there is either a lack
这个红色的是说要么是没有
of constraints or conflicting constraints,
的约束或相互矛盾的约束,
In other words, there are constraint problems that are
换句话说,有约束的问题
so bad that your app is not going to work when you run,
如此糟糕,当你运行你的应用程序不会工作,
So we can click on this red thing and it will show us
所以我们可以点击这个红色的东西,它会告诉我们
all the details of all the constraint problems,
所有的约束的所有细节问题,
So now when we mouse over this,
现在当我们鼠标,
it still says need constraints for x position,
还是说需要约束x的位置,
But we can find out which stack view it's talking about,
但我们可以找出哪些堆栈视图的谈论,
And of course, it's talking about that one,
当然,这是谈论这个,
This other stack view over here,
这里的其他堆栈视图,
it has an x position, it's tied to the left edge,
它有一个x位置,与左边缘,
But this one is not tied to anything,
但这个不是绑定到任何东西,
It's top and bottom are tied but
顶部和底部是但挂钩
it could be sliding horizontally any which way,
可以是任何水平滑动,
So that's not tied, so
所以这不是挂钩,所以
we don't know where it's exposition is supposed to be,
我们不知道它是博览会应该是,
We need to fix that,
我们需要解决这个问题,
How are we gonna fix that?
我们要如何解决这个问题?
Well probably the best way to do that is to hook it up to
可能最好的办法,是连接到
the edge of this stack view,
这个堆栈视图的边缘,
Cuz if it, we tie this edge right here to this stack view,
因为如果它,我们把这个优势这个堆栈视图,
then it'll, its horizontal position will be set because
然后它会,将因为它的水平位置
it'll be tied to this guy's horizontal position,
它会与这个人的水平位置,
So how do we hook this guy up to here?
那么我们如何这家伙了吗?
Well we could of course control drag, all right, but
当然我们可以控制拖,好吧,但是
I'm gonna use this opportunity to show you a different way to
我要利用这个机会向你展示一个不同的方式
Which is I selected it and I'm going down to this other menu
这是我选择它,我要到另一个菜单吗
hook it up,
钩,
down here, this one that says add new constraints, and
这里,这个说增加新的约束,
I'm clicking on it,
我点击它,
And we've actually seen this one briefly, I think,
我们已经看到这个简单,我认为,
But here you can do things like make things to be
但是在这里你可以让事情
affixed with,
贴,
Or you can set the distance from your nearest neighbor,
或者你可以设置你的最近邻距离,
That's what these are,
这就是这些,
These are the distance to the nearest neighbor,
这些都是距离最近的邻居,
Now these little red I-beams are all grayed out right here
现在这些小红焊接都是灰色的
or transparency'd out,
或者透明度会出来,
So right now,
现在,
this guy is not hooked up to his nearest neighbor at all,
这家伙不是连接到最近的邻居,
But we clearly wanna hook him up to his nearest neighbor on
但我们显然想钩他最近的邻居
the right, that's this one,
正确的,这是这一个,
So, I'm gonna click this I-beam,it turns it on and now,
点击这个工字梁,它在现在,
he's clamped to his nearest neighbor on the right and
他是他右边最近邻和夹紧
he's eight pixels away because that's what the dash
他因为这就是dash 8像素
blue lines put, but we dont want that,
蓝线,但是我们不希望这样,
we want ten pixels away, so we're gonna put ten,
我们想要10个像素,所以我们要把十个,
We have 10 pixels away clamped to the nearest neighbor,
我们有10个像素夹到最近的邻居,
Let's add that constraint as well,
让我们添加约束,
Our red went away but now we have yellow,
我们的红色走了但是现在我们有黄色,
What does yellow mean in auto layout?
在自动布局黄色是什么意思?
Yellow means, "your constraints are okay and
好吧,黄色的意思,“你的约束
when you run it's probably gonna work, but
当您运行可能会工作,但
what you're looking at in your storyboard is not
你看到在你的故事板不是
what your constraints are saying",
你的约束在说什么”,
Your constraints are not equal to what you see here,
你的约束不等于你在这里看到的,
You can see right here, for example, it's expecting
你可以看到在这里,例如,它的期望
the X position of this stack view that's highlighted right
高亮显示的这个堆栈视图的X位置正确
here to be at 385, but it's actually at 387,
在385年,但它实际上是在387年,
And if we zoom way in, in fact, with option,
如果我们放大方式,事实上,与选择,
There's a option zooming here,
这里有一个选择缩放,
You can see there's a dashed yellow line,
你可以看到有一个黄色虚线,
I don't know if you can see that,
我不知道你是否能看到,
Yeah, you can see that,
是的,你可以看到,
This dashed yellow line, that's where the constraint
这个黄色虚线,这就是约束
system thinks this Stack View should be,
系统认为这个堆栈视图应该,
The solid yellow line is where it actually is,
固体黄线是实际的地方,
And even the i-beam between the two has a little -2
甚至两者之间的工字梁有一个小2
right there, saying yeah, I got this i-beam here, but
说,是的,我这里的工字梁,但是
it seems like it should be 2 points over to the left,
它似乎应该是2点左边,
How do we fix this,
我们如何解决这个问题,
When we have these yellow problems how do we
当我们有这些黄色的问题我们如何
get things to be put in the right place or something,
把事情放在正确的位置,
And the answer is we're gonna go over to our document
答案是,我们要去我们的文档
outline,
轮廓,
By the way we can get here with the same way we got
顺便说一下我们可以在同样的方式
to the red by clicking in this upper corner with the yellow,
点击在这上红色角落的黄色,
And we're gonna click on this triangle cuz that's gonna,
我们要点击这个三角形因为会,
the string will let you resolve the problem,
绳子会让你解决问题,
So, I click on it and actually have some choices
所以,我点击它实际上有一些选择
how to resolve that problem, one is I can update the frame,
如何解决这个问题,一个是我可以更新框架,
that means move the views to match the constrains,
这意味着移动视图匹配约束,
which is definitely what I want in this case,
在这种情况下,绝对是我想要的
Because I do want it to be 10 pixels apart there not eight,
因为我想要10个像素没有八,
But I could also do other things like
但是我也可以做其他的事情
updating the constraints,
更新的限制,
And that would go and
这就去
Even thought I typed 10, this would clamp it back to 8, so
甚至以为我输入10,这将夹回8,所以
that it would match what's going on here,
这是怎么回事,它将匹配,
Or you can do the dreaded reset to suggested
或者你可以做可怕的重置
constraints,
的限制,
Which probably also would at least do that,
也可能至少会这样做,
probably do some other things we don't want,
可能我们不希望做一些其他的事情,
In other words it kinda try do what the blue line said,
换句话说,它有点尝试做蓝线表示,
Reset to suggest the constraints we rarely use,
重置建议我们很少使用的约束,
It's only good for when you're
只有当你
like dragging something right into the middle or
像拖到中间或东西
right out to the edges those kind of things,
对边缘的东西,
It's not super good guessing what you want
这不是超级好猜你想要的
in other scenarios,
在其他情况下,
Now, this update frames, I can apply it just to
现在,这个更新框架,我可以将它应用到
this view right here that's having the problem or
这个观点有问题或
I can apply it to all the views in my entire controller,
我可以把它应用在我的整个控制器的所有视图,
And whether you have this switched or not,
你是否有这个交换,
it's about 50/50 when we switch this is whether you
当我们50/50开关这是你
have other views that you're in the middle of working on,
有其他观点,你在工作,
That you haven't quite fully specified their constraints,
你还没完全指定他们的约束,
Then you'd probably don't want apply to all,
然后你可能不想要适用于所有,
because it's going to try to move them and
因为这是要他们和移动
you haven't finished specifying them,
你还没完成指定他们,
But in this case,
但在这种情况下,
this is the only view that has any misplaced views, you see,
这是唯一的观点有错误的观点,你看,
So, I can go ahead and say all or not,
所以,我可以继续说,
It's not going to make a difference,
它不会改变
because this is the only one that is going to move,
因为这是唯一一个会移动,
I'm just going to leave it at all,
我要离开,
And I'm gonna say Fix,
我会说修复,
And you're gonna see that it moved it,
你会看到它移动,
Moved it two pixels over here,
这两个像素,
If we zoom in again here,
如果我们在这里再次放大,
we'll see now that this is tan, just like this is ten,
现在我们将会看到这是棕褐色的,就像这是10,
And it also says No Autolayout issues over here,
还说没有自动布局问题,
It moved it,
移动它,
If we go back here, there's nothing in the corner,
如果我们回到这里,没有什么在角落里,
All is well,
一切都好,
We're in good shape right there,
我们的身体状况很好,
Now, there's one other problem with this,
现在还有一个问题,
look how narrow these buttons are compared to these buttons,
看这些按钮,这些按钮比较窄
We want these buttons to be exactly the same width
我们希望这些按钮完全相同的宽度
as all of these buttons,
所有的这些按钮,
Now since it's not in the same stack view it's not getting
现在,因为它不是在相同的堆栈视图是没有得到
the fill equally and so it's not getting that,
填充同样不是得到,
So, how can I make these buttons inside this
所以,我怎么能让这些按钮在这个
stack view right here be exactly the same width
堆栈视图在这里是完全相同的宽度
as the buttons over here,
的按钮,
Well, I'm going to just control drag,
好吧,我只是控制拖动,
Actually, I'm gonna control drag from the entire
实际上,我要从整个控制拖动
stack view,
堆栈视图,
See I'm dragging from the stack view,
看到我从堆栈视图拖拽,
To any button over here and just say
在这里只说任何按钮
that I want it to be the same width as any button over here,
我想要任何按钮,宽度一样
So, we'll just pick this one and
所以,我们就拿这一个
here's all the things we can choose and
这是我们可以选择的一切
then I'm gonna go down here to the bottom and
然后我要去下面和底部
pick Equal Widths okay cuz I want those
选择相同宽度好因为我想要这些
buttons to be the same width,
按钮是相同的宽度,
And I'm gonna add that constraint and
我要添加约束和
it applies the constraint,
它适用于约束,
And you can even see this constraint right there,
你甚至可以看到这个约束,
Again, I'll zoom in,
再次,我将放大,
You can see the constraints right here,
你可以看到这里的约束,
This equals and
这等于
this equals are saying those two things are equal,
这等于说这两件事是相等的,
So we're almost there,
所以我们几乎在那里,
We've got these four buttons that we've added
我们有这四个按钮,我们补充道
looking like they're in the stack view by putting our own
看起来像他们在堆栈视图通过将自己的
constraints on there,
限制,
The only thing that's left is,
唯一剩下的是,
we're not using the whole space,
我们不使用整个空间,
We're not connected to the whole space,
我们不是连接到整个空间,
Now here, we can do exactly what we did before,
现在,我们能做什么,
I'm just gonna select this StackView right here,
我要选择这个StackView,
Not this one, but just this one,
不是这一个,只是这一个,
I'm gonna Ctrl drag up to here and
我要Ctrl拖到这里
I'm gonna set its vertical spacing,
我要设置它的垂直间距,
Put's this I-beam in here to the top,
在这里把这是工字梁,
Now when I double-click on it,
现在我双击它,
Well also by the way, you know that we can click on these and
也顺便说一下,你知道我们可以点击这些
inspect them, remember that, so it's showing that this
检查他们,记住,这是显示这个
I-beam connects the stack views top to the displays
工字梁连接堆栈视图顶部显示
button and it sets them to be equal with an offset of 57,
按钮,它集相等的抵消57岁
That's what this constant is,
这就是这个常数,
It's an offset of 57,
这是一个抵消57,
So that's why we're getting this 57 high bar,
这就是为什么我们要这57高酒吧,
And we don't want that,
我们不希望这样,
We want to change that to be standard value,
我们想要改变这种标准的价值,
Actually, we don't even want standard value,
实际上,我们甚至不需要标准的价值,
we probably want 10 because we probably want this distance to
我们可能要10因为我们可能希望这个距离
be the same as the distance between all of our buttons,
同我们所有的按钮之间的距离,
I'm not sure which one we want but
我不确定哪一个我们想要的
I think that one's probably pretty good,
我认为一个人的可能很好,
So that's good now notice as soon as constrained the top of
这很好现在注意一旦受限的顶部
this stack view to go up here it automatically dragged
这个堆栈视图上它自动拖
this stack view's top up there,
这个堆栈视图的顶部,
That's because we have a constrained
那是因为我们有一个限制
that hooks the tops of these together,
钩子顶部的这些在一起,
If I click on here, I look in the size inspector,
如果我点击这里,我看大小检查员,
you can see that I've got a line top to this top and
你可以看到我有一条线从上到上面
bottom to this other stack view,
这个其他堆栈视图,
Do you see that?
你看到了吗?
So that's good,
这很好,
What about this edge?
这条边呢?
Same thing here, we can just take this stack view and
这里也一样,我们可以把这个堆栈视图和
hook it to edge, this leading space to contain a margin,
钩边,这导致空间包含一个保证金,
just like we did before, and
就像我们之前做的,
here we get this, obviously we can inspect it over here,
这里我们得到这个,很明显我们可以检查它,
We can also double click on it to inspect it, which
我们也可以双击它检查它,
we saw before, and here I've picked standard value, there's
我们之前看到的,在这里我选择了标准的价值,有
no standard value available, so I'm just gonna do zero and
没有标准的价值,所以我要做零和
it's gonna zoom that think over,
它会放大,仔细考虑,
That's it,
就是这样,
So we've done everything we need to do no for
所以我们需要做我们所做的一切没有了
this height-compact situation,
这height-compact的情况,
And so,
所以,
this is a very important thing to remember to do,
这是一个非常重要的是要记住,
When you're done, click Done varying down here,
当你完成,点击完成不同,
Because a lot of times you'll do this,
因为很多时候你会这样做,
and you're like all right it's working,
你喜欢好的工作,
And then, you'll go on to work on some other sized class, and
然后,你会继续工作在其他的类,和
you'll forgot to have clicked this off,
你会忘记了点击这个,
And now, you'll be editing only in the height-compact,
现在,你只会编辑height-compact,
So, we're gonna hit Done varying,
所以,我们要做不同的,
Get's rid of our blue,
摆脱我们的蓝色,
And we, so we know we're in good shape,
我们,所以我们知道我们的身体状况很好,
Now what happens if I go back to portrait?
现在如果我回到画像吗?
What's this gonna look like in portrait?
这是什么画像会怎么样?
Anyone wanna volunteer?
有人想做志愿者吗?
Yes, so all of this work that we did here
是的,所以我们在这里做所有这些工作
has had no effect whatsoever on portrait,
对肖像没有任何效果,
Because portrait is height regular,
因为肖像是高度固定,
And all that work we did here, every single bit we did since
和我们在这里做的工作,我们做的每一位
we clicked into the blue bar, only happens in high compact,
我们点击蓝色的酒吧,只发生在高紧凑,
So when we click back to portrait it looks just like it
所以当我们点击回到肖像看起来就像它
used to, unaffected by all that work we did,
习惯,影响工作,
Make sense, understand why that happened?
意义,理解为什么,发生了什么?
So now, we need to, in this case, the height regular case,
现在,我们需要,在这种情况下,常规情况下,高度
we need to put those buttons in along the top here,
我们需要把这些按钮在顶部,
So, I'm gonna do this pretty quickly, so
所以,我要做这个很快,所以
you can kind of see a review of it,
你可以看到一个评论,
Actually, before I do that review,
实际上,之前我做评论,
let's let this soak in a little bit,
让我们让这个浸泡在一点,
because I wanna show you the document outline,
因为我想向您展示文档大纲,
So, I'm going over the document outline and
所以,我要在文档大纲和
I'm just gonna make it wider,
我要让它更广泛,
And why do you wanna make this wider?
为什么你想让这个更广泛?
Well, the document outline shows not only all your views,
嗯,不仅文档大纲显示你所有的观点,
but it also show all of your constraints,
但它也显示你所有的约束,
You see all these constraints down here?
你在这里看到所有这些限制?
And you notice that some of them are, like,
你注意到一些,,
grayed out here,
灰色的,
And why are they grayed out?
为什么他们是灰色的吗?
Because they apply to a different size class
因为他们适用于不同大小的类
than is being shown here,
比所示,
We are looking at height regular, these grayed out
我们看着高度固定,这些灰色的
constraints are only over here in height compact,
限制只有在高度紧凑,
So, when we go to height compact,
所以,当我们去高度紧凑,
all of them apply because we haven't done any
所有这些,因为我们还没有做任何申请
constraints that are in height regular only yet,
还只在高度常规约束,
So, all of these apply in that circumstance,
所以,所有这些应用在这种情况下,
Now, looking at your constraints
现在,看你的约束
right here is a really good kind of tool for
这里是一个很好的工具
finding tiny little problems with your UI,
你的UI,发现小问题
And that's when you have magic numbers,
当你有神奇的数字,
You see this magic numbers in here?
你看到这个神奇的数字在这里吗?
8 8 20 10 and 10,
8 8 20 10和10个,
By the way, we never wanna look at the magic numbers for
顺便说一下,我们从来没有想看看神奇的数字
things that are grade out,
年级的事情了,
Like this 347 when I look at that because it
这样347当我看着,因为它
doesn't apply here,
不适用,
We only wanna look at the ones that are dark blue here,
我们只是想看看那些深蓝色,
So we don't like to see these magic numbers here,
所以我们不喜欢看到这些神奇的数字,
unless we intend for that magic number to be there,
除非我们打算让这神奇的数字,
So, 8 8 20, we never typed those in,
8 8 20,我们从来没有类型的,
Why are they there?
为什么他们那里?
We don't want them there,
我们不希望他们在那里,
10 and 10 however we do want those,
10和10然而我们想要这些,
We wanted those,
我们想要这些,
those are a magic number we want in our UI,
这是一个神奇的数字我们想要在我们的界面,
That's our spacing in between that we decided we want,
这是我们之间的间距,我们决定我们想要的,
So, how to we get rid of these magic numbers, like 8, 8, 20?
我们如何摆脱这些神奇的数字,像8日8日20吗?
Well, you're gonna click on them to select it,
好吧,你要点击以选择它,
This is just like if you had clicked on it in here,
这就像如果你点击它,
cuz the document outline, you remember, you click there,
因为文档大纲,你记住,你点击那里,
It's just like you're clicking in, in here, except for
就像你点击,在这里,除了
sometimes it's even easier to click on the document outline,
有时是更容易点击文档大纲,
We could also click on the thing that it's attached to
我们也可以点击它连着
like the display,
像显示,
So, this is the display's top equals top layout
所以,这是显示顶级=布局
guide plus eight,
指导+ 8,
And go to the size inspector here and see it,
去这里的尺寸检查器,看看它,
And we'll see the magic numbers here also,
我们还会看到神奇的数字,
not just in the document outline,
不仅在文档大纲,
But, we're seeing them here in our size inspector,
但是,我们看到他们在我们尺寸检查器,
So, any time we see these magic numbers we want to
所以,任何时候我们想看到这些神奇的数字
inspect them,
检查他们,
either here or by clicking on them and edit them,
在这里或通过单击它们和编辑它们,
So, in the size inspector
所以,在尺寸检查器
we've always gone in to check to make sure things are good,
我们一直在检查,以确保一切都不错,
but we can also change them if they're not good,
但是我们也可以改变他们如果他们不是好,
And so, here I'm clicking on it and editing it, and
所以,这里我点击它和编辑它,和
this constant, I don't want it to be eight, so
这个常数,我不希望它是8
let's see what my choices are,
让我们看看什么是我的选择,
I don't have standard value, use canvas value means
我没有标准的价值,使用帆布值的含义
use what's currently showing in the story board,
在故事板,使用目前的表现
we rarely want that,
我们很少想要,
It's almost never want that,
这几乎是从来没有希望,
that would mean that we had to have dragged it right in
这意味着我们不得不拖着它的
position they will use the blue lines,
他们将利用蓝线位置,
It might be right but,
这或许是对的,但
almost never do you want the canvas value,
几乎从来没有你想要帆布值,
Instead, we're gonna do what we do here,
相反,我们要做我们所做的,
to say what we want, so maybe, this one, actually I'm gonna
说我们想要的,所以,这一个,我要
do this one down here first, let's look at this one,
先做这个下面,让我们来看看这个,
So this top layout guide here, this one, we can use
这里上面的布局指导,这个,我们可以使用
a standard value, to do it to the top layout guide,
一个标准的价值,它的布局指导,
And look, I did standard value and
看,我的价值和标准
it got rid of the plus eight,
它摆脱了+ 8,
It's still eight pixel, eight points over there because that
它仍然是八个像素,因为8分
is the standard value but it stopped showing it as that,
是标准的价值但它停止显示它,
And same thing up here when we go up to this one and we look,
和上面一样,当我们去这一个,我们看,
there's no standard value here so what do we put, 0,
这里没有标准的价值我们说,0,
And we will have zero,
,我们将为零,
That actually fixed a bug because it move this display
其实固定一个缺陷,因为它移动这个显示
right up to the edge right there,
到边缘,
And you can see that got rid of that one,
你可以看到,摆脱了这个,
Same thing here, we can go to this one,
同样的事情,我们可以去,
Let's do this one by inspecting it,
让我们做一个通过检查它,
Here's the constant right here, 20, we don't want that,
这是常数,20岁,我们不希望这样,
We go here and say, standard value,
我们去这里说,标准的价值,
What's the standard value and the 20 is gone,
什么标准的价值和20,
that also fixed a bug
固定一个bug
cuz the thing was not all the way down at the bottom,
因为事就没有在底部,
So, you see how we fixed bugs by going and
所以,你看我们如何去和修复bug
chasing down all of our magic numbers in this view,
追踪所有的魔法数字在这个视图中,
okay in the document outline,
好的文档大纲,
So, you almost always want to be chasing those things down,
所以,你总是想要追逐那些东西,
The only problem can happen here when you're chasing them
唯一的问题可能发生在这里当你追逐他们
is when you have a magic number like 8 or
是当你有一个神奇的数字8或吗
20 that you actually intend to be 8 or 20,
20,你真的打算是8到20,
Cuz then you're like is that a magic wand or not?
因为你像一个魔杖吗?
Because there's no way to down like a variable in
因为没有办法像一个变量
there or something,
之类的,
But these tens, we know those are right,
但这些数以千万计,我们知道那些是正确的,
All right, so,
好吧,那么,
just a little side track there to show you how to use that,
只是一个小旁轨向您展示如何使用,
Let's go back to our height regular and
让我们回到我们的常规和高度
make this look like what we want,
让这看起来像我们想要的,
So, let's start by pasting back in these things,
那么,让我们先粘贴在这些事情,
Actually, before we do that,
实际上,在我们这么做之前,
And this is a common mistake you'll make to,
这是一个常见的错误你会赚,
What mistake did I make right there?
我做了什么错误?
I wanted to start doing height regular and
我想开始做定期和高度
I didn't hit vary for traits, so
我没有达到不同的特征,因此
I wasn't acctually editing height regular,
我没有编辑高度固定,实际上,
I was editing any/any,
我是编辑任何/,
So, don't miss that, so I'm gonna vary for
所以,不要错过,所以我要改变
traits in heights and
特征的高度和
this gonna use this height were I'm looking at, height
这将使用这个高度是我在看,高度
regular this gonna show me all gonna show me all devices with
定期都要给我要给我的所有设备
height regular which is all the iPads, Split View,
高度一般都是ipad,拆分视图,
Masters, all the iPhone, they're all height regulars,
大师们,所有的iPhone,他们都高度常客,
So it's just showing me and
所以它只是显示我
I can actually do this editing in anyone of those,
我可以做这个编辑在任何人的,
Because they're all height regular,
因为它们都是高度固定,
All right, so now let's paste this in,
好了,现在让我们粘贴的,
Now, when I pasted this in,
现在,当我贴,
by the way an interesting thing happened,
顺便说一下,发生了一件有趣的事
If I go to my attributes inspector and
如果我去我的属性检查器
go all the way to the bottom,
一路走到底,
Look right here,
看这里,
Okay, I selected this stake view right here,
好吧,我选择这个股份视图,
And you see that it says installed not,
你看到它说没有安装,
But, in height regular it's installed,
但是,在高度正常安装,
That's saying this stack view only is installed in the view
说这个堆栈视图只是安装在视图
hierarchy,
层次结构,
When we're height regular,
当我们高度固定,
If I click on this one notice it's installed everywhere,
如果我点击这个通知安装无处不在,
Doesn't say not installed and height regular,
并不是说没有安装和高度,
It says installed everywhere,
它说安装无处不在,
So, you can always tell which user and
所以,你可以总是告诉用户和
you can of course click these on and off,
当然你可以点击这些了,
And you can even add a plus here to add variation
你甚至可以添加一个+添加变异
to remove them,
删除它们,
I find it easier just to Enter this varying mode and
我发现它更容易进入这个模式和不同
then drag these things in,
然后拖动这些东西,
Anyway, here we go,
不管怎样,好了,
Let's get this thing down here,
下面让我们这个东西,
Again, we want the both edges to be lined up,
再一次,我们想要两个边排队,
So, let's go ahead and
所以,让我们继续
do that remember we do that by selecting them both,
记得我们做选择,
And in going over here to a line,
在这里到一条线,
This time it's the leading and
这一次是领先的
trailing edges that we want to be the same,
我们想要同样的后缘,
And add those constraints,
并添加这些约束,
Again, as soon as I had those constraints now I have
再次,一旦我有现在这些约束我
a problem with a vertical position of this stack view,
一个问题这个堆栈视图的垂直位置,
is not defined,
没有定义,
You need constraints for the Y position,
你需要为Y位置约束,
Cuz, I've only constrained it horizontally right there,
因为,我只限制水平,
So, let's go ahead and constrain it for
所以,让我们去限制它
a vertical by pinning it to this,
一个垂直固定它,
So, I'm gonna use this other one over here this time,
所以,我要用这里的另一个,
And I'm gonna show you something interesting here,
这里我要告诉你一些有趣的事情,
So, here I'm gonna pin to its bottom nearest neighbor, and
这里我要销其最近的邻居,和
I'm gonna use ten, which is my magic number that I want,
我要用十个,这是我神奇的数字,我想要的,
And I'm gonna pick something in here cuz remember last time
我会选择在这里因为记得上次的东西
we did this and
我们这样做,
when I put this in here it turned from red to yellow,
当我在这里把这个结果从红色到黄色,
Because things weren't in the right position cuz I had added
因为事情没有在正确的位置因为我有补充道
constraints and it didn't move them,
约束和它没有移动它们,
Well, if you go down here and say update frames either to
好吧,如果你去这里,要么说更新帧
the items of the new constraints,
项目的新限制,
involved in the new constraints which would be,
参与新约束,
This nearest neighbor and us, or
或者,这最近邻和美国
you can do it all the frames in your container,
你能做到所有的帧在你的容器,
If you turn this on, then when you add this constraints,
如果你把这个,当你添加这个限制,
it will automatically move them,
它会自动移动,
And then, you won't get the yellow,
然后,你不会得到黄色,
You won't have to go over and
你没有去
click, update frames and all that,
点击,更新帧,
So watch this, when I add this constraint, it moved them,
所以看这个,当我添加这个约束,它感动他们,
You see that?
你看到了吗?
No yellow,
没有黄色的,
Right here, I am in
在这里,我在
my document outline nothing on in the upper corner
我的文档大纲上角落里什么也没有
like there was when we did the other one,
就像当我们做另一个,
Now, we still have one other things to do here,
现在,我们仍然有一个其他的事情要做,
It's not obvious that we need to do this but
这不是明显,我们需要这样做
the height of these just happens to to be the same
这些恰好的高度是一样的
height as all of these,
所有这些高度,
But that's just happy circumstance,
但这只是幸福的情况下,
And the other time it was obvious that they weren't,
和其他时间他们不很明显,
So I need to do the same thing here where I'm gonna control,
所以我需要做同样的事,我要控制,
drag from this stack view,
从这个堆栈视图拖拽,
And then again I could do either an individual button or
然后我可以做一个单独的按钮或
one of these sub stack views right here,
这些子堆栈视图之一,
And I'm gonna set them to be equal heights,
我要把它们相等的高度,
Other was, just so that no matter what
其他,这样不管什么
mathematical symbol I put in those buttons up there
数学符号我放在这些按钮
then it's never gonna squinch down and be smaller,
那就不会突角拱下来更小,
Or grow up and be bigger than the other ones,
或长大的,比其他的更大,
So I'm gonna say equal height right there,
所以我想说平等的高度,
See the two equals that got generated there?
看到两个等于一个生成的?
So same thing as before,
所以之前一样,
We've done a good job of adding this on and
我们已经添加这个,做了很好的工作
making it seem like this is part of the stack view,
使它看起来像这是堆栈视图的一部分,
So this time we're going to attach this stack view up to
所以这次我们要附上这个堆栈视图
here,
在这里,
So I'm just gonna control drag up to here,
所以我要控制拖到这里,
set the vertical spacing, and I'm gonna put the edge of this
设置垂直间距,我要把它的边缘
big stack view right here over to the edge,
大堆栈视图到边缘,
And same thing as always we want to double click here,
和一样总是我们想双击这里,
Standard if we can,
如果我们能标准,
We can't, we'll do zero,
我们不能,我们要做零,
Same thing with this one over here,
和这个一样,
Double click,
双击,
Here we want our magic number of ten,
在这里,我们希望我们的神奇数字10,
So now we've done all that we need to do for
现在我们已经做了所有我们需要做的
our height regulars so we can done varying right here,
我们的常客所以我们可以做不同的高度,
And did this effect height compact, no,
和这样做效果高度紧凑,不,
no effect on height compact,
不影响高度紧凑,
And if we run, we've got width is compact but
如果我们跑步,紧凑但我们有宽度
height is regular so we're getting five high and
高度是常规的所以我们要五高
four across, in a regular height we go five high,
四,在常规的高度我们五高,
And when we switch over here, we get width compact,
当我们这里的开关,我们得到宽度紧凑,
height compact and we're gonna to four high and five across,
高度紧凑,我们要到四和五高,
Hopefully that showed you pretty much all
你希望显示几乎所有
the things you need to know about auto layout,
你需要知道的事情自动布局,
Not just how we vary major UI differences between
不仅我们如何改变主要界面之间的差异
the size classes,
大小类,
But also how you are gonna use the document outline over
而且你会如何使用文档大纲
here to look at all of your constraints,
来看看你所有的约束,
And fix the dark blue ones that have magic numbers that
并修复深蓝色的有魔力的数字
you didn't intend,
你没有打算,
You can also use this to click on your constraints and
您还可以使用该约束和点击
look at them,
看看他们,
It's highlighting them here,
它强调了,
And inspect them over here,
并检查它们,
And we're still often using the size inspector,
和我们仍然经常使用尺寸检查器,
right here, to look at all of our constraints,
在这里,看看我们所有的约束,
In the hugging priority we briefly showed that's just if
在拥抱的优先级,我们短暂显示,只是如果
you have two things that are trying to share a space,
你有两件事要共享一个空间,
And you want one to hug and one to use the other space,
你想要一个拥抱和一个用另一个空间,
you can do the hugging,
你可以拥抱,
We also didn't really talk about the content compression
我们还没有真正谈论的内容压缩
resistance but that's the opposite thing,
阻力但相反的事情,
That's where it's trying to collapse things down,
这就是它的崩溃下来,
One of them wants to keep its height and
其中一个想保持高度和
the other one is happy to be collapsed down,
另一个是高兴倒塌下来,
So that's just kinda the opposite of hugging,
这只是有点相反的拥抱,
That compressing so we can set that as well,
压缩,所以我们可以设置,
Any questions about all that autolayout business?
所有的自动布局业务方面有问题吗?
Okay, so that is it for the demo,
好了,这是为了演示,
And just a little bit about what's coming up,
就一下接下来会发生什么,
So tomorrow your assignment five is due by midnight,
所以明天你的作业5将在午夜,
No section Friday this week,
本周星期五没课,
Next week the lectures are gonna be about animation,
下个星期的讲座是动画,
A really important part obviously of an iPhone device
很显然iPhone设备的重要组成部分
or iOS device is animating things on screen,
或iOS设备是动画的东西在屏幕上,
So we're gonna talk about that next week,
所以我们要讨论,下周,
>> For more, please visit us at stanford,edu,
> >更多内容,请访问我们的斯坦福大学edu,